forexminute.com 2015-12-19

# Privacy Policy | ForexMinute

Global Invest Limited. (Hereinafter “FOREXMINUTE” or “FOREXMINUTE.COM” or “the Company” or “Global Invest Ltd.” or “Global Invest” or “we”) is the owner of the website forexminute.com (“The website”). This “Privacy Policy” describes how we collect, store and use information on individuals that use this Web Site. Global Invest is committed to protecting your privacy.

###  GLOBAL INVEST Privacy Pledge

The term “personal data” as used in this Policy refers to information such as your name, e-mail address or mailing address, or any data that can be used to identify you. We ensure that our staff and those acting on our behalf obtain, use and disclose personal information lawfully and correctly.

### Right of Information

The Company informs you that the collection and processing of personal data is aimed at providing you with services offered by this website and to send you commercial information on products or services you may be interested in. The Company will store these data as long as it is reasonably necessary to attain the mentioned purposes and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical requirement.

### Consent to Use Information

By using this Web Site, or providing information to us in other formats, you consent to the collection and use of this information by The Company. In addition, you are committed to supplying true, complete and accurate information and to keeping it up to date.

### Mandatory and Optional Information

In order to use our services, users may be asked to fill in a form, which requires providing certain personal information to The Company. Unless otherwise provided in those fields expressly marked with an asterisk (*), answers to our questions on personal data are not mandatory. Not supplying the information required in such optional fields shall not represent any decrease of the services and information that we may provide. However, failure to complete those compulsory fields or providing incorrect personal data shall prevent us from providing the requested information or services.

### Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Objection

The Company informs you of the possibility of exercising your rights to access, rectify, cancel and object to the processing of your personal data simply by making a written request to ForexMinute.com using our contact us page. Your requests will be dealt with in a prompt and proper manner. 

###  Security and Confidentiality

The Company guarantees that your personal data will be treated with the strictest confidentiality, and that the server in which these data will be stored and dealt with has implemented the necessary industry-standard security measures to prevent accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access to the above-mentioned data.

###  Cookies and Spamming

This Web Site does not use “cookies” to gather personal information such as a person’s name or email address. A “cookie” is a small text file placed on your computer’s hard drive or browser by a webpage server. The cookies on this website are used to hide certain publicity from the users that have chosen this option. The cookies are also used to save the identity of the user in order to allow automatic login to the private home page of the registered user, but only if this is desired.

### Sharing Information with Our Affiliates

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as informing customers about new products and services, or to aid in the trading activity of the company, its affiliates, or employees, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies that have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above.

Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent Global Invest does in accordance with this Policy. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

Global Invest does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that Global Invest dictates. 

Global Invest reserve the right to sell such information to third parties who might be interested in offering its services to Global Invest’s Customers of which Global Invest find appropriate to offer its customer base. Global Invest may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your express consent.

###  Links to Other Websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to this Web Site, excluding third party websites, as we may provide links to other websites which we believe may be of interest to our visitors. We aim at ensuring that such websites are of the highest standard. However, due to the natureof the World Wide Web, we cannot guarantee the standards of every linked website or be responsible for their content.

###  Updates to this Policy

Should THE COMPANY amend this Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to new legal requirements, we will immediately post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we gather, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
